All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
During their journey to the New World, Luffy and his crew arrive on Fishman Island, which is located 10,000 meters below sea level.
There, they found themselves facing the New Fishman Pirates, who were looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom and instigated an all-out war.
After a long and grueling battle, Luffy finally defeated Hordy, the captain of the New Fishman Pirates, thwarting their plan for revenge.
Two years ago, up in Shandora, I read a poneglyph that located one of the ancient weapons.
This mermaid princess who lived during the same time as Joy Boy.
She was known by another name as well, wasn't she?
Wasn't she?
She is the ancient weapon.
Poseidon!
The Straw Hat stunned!
The new Fleet Admiral of the Navy!
Many years ago, for some unknown purpose, there were three powerful entities that could destroy this entire world.
They were ancient weapons named after gods. Pluton, Uranus, and Poseidon.
And one of those great weapons is… the princess.
Indeed.
Well, if that's the case, we can't let anyone else know about this.
If we did, the government and every other organization would want Shirahoshi for themselves, not to mention other pirates.
Ancient weapons? Strong enough to destroy the whole world?
To think I was just going to take off after stealing all their silly trinkets!
How foolish of me! I almost overlooked the most valuable item they've got!
That mermaid princess is more precious than I imagined!
Yee-haw!
Whew! I think I can go for another plate!
Don't tell me you've scarfed down that much food already!
Can you blame me? It's all so good! I can eat this stuff until I die!
Especially the candy!
It's as good as meat! I'll take a hundred more!
Wh-well, actually, I'm afraid we've just about run out of the candy!
But I'd be happy to bring you something else to eat if you'd like me to!
Okay, sure!
Tell me something, Luffy!
Why you sit here stuffing your face?
Are you aware of all that's been happening in the world?
Huh? What are you getting at, Jinbei?
Ah, so you're completely uninformed!
That's a problem, but I can't say I'm shocked!
I'm lost!
We brought you more food, Luffy!
Come with me!
Sure! Just give me a second!
I'm gonna take this one to go!
Hey!
Hmm?
You guys left the party, too?
I'm trying to sober up.
I drank too much.
And I ate too much!
Sanji flirted too much!
This place is so magical!
There's so many babes!
I can't take it!
What?!
Chilaka, Inu, and Aokiji fought each other?!
It was a major event!
Did Rayleigh never mention this to you during your training?
Nope!
This is news to me!
That was cruel of him!
Oh, I knew about it the whole time!
So did I do good?!
That's crazy!
It all started two years ago, right after the war ended.
Sengoku resigned as Fleet Admiral.
Aokiji was well-liked among his own men, so Sengoku nominated him to take over the title.
But many high-ranking officials favored Aka Inu, so he became a contender as well.
Aokiji is normally cool-tempered, but he was quite adamant in his disapproval of Aka Inu.
He found him unfit for the position.
So it did not take long for the disagreement to come to blows on an island somewhere.
It was the first and final battle between the two admirals.
It was agreed that whoever lost would withdraw his candidacy without protest.
And the winner would become the leader of the Navy.
As the rest of the world now knows, they fought for ten whole days.
The two opponents were equally matched in power.
But the duel finally ended.
Aka Inu, or as some know him, Sakazuki, emerged victorious.
That bastard won!
I'm putting an end to this!
So did he kill Aokiji?
Well, both admirals were severely injured.
In fact, Aokiji couldn't even stand after it was over.
However, Aka Inu was strangely merciful towards him.
Despite this, Aokiji refused to accept the result.
He has resigned from the Navy.
I can't believe Aokiji would just up and quit like that.
Indeed.
I wonder what's been going through his mind since then.
The government has certainly lost a valuable asset.
You can say that again.
The admirals were the main reason the Navy was so powerful, weren't they?
At first, yes.
But they have found ways to overcompensate in Aokiji's absence.
One might argue that they're more dangerous than ever now.
There is still much you do not know.
Listen closely.
Before you reach the New World,
you must be aware of two key changes that have occurred there.
Now then, the first matter, as I've already begun to explain,
is that the Navy under Fleet Admiral Sakazuki is stronger than before.
And secondly, the Blackbeard Pirates are making strides of their own.
Those guys again?
You mean the ones we met back in Mocktown?
They attacked my homeland. I can never forget them.
I can never forget them.
This new era they keep rambling on and on about is a load of crap.
The era when pirates dream of treasure will come to an end?
Right!
What are you talking about?
The dreams of pirates will never end!
So you're...
Blackbeard!
Huh?
Oh, right. I guess I never gave you my name, did I?
Z-hahaha! Long time no see, Straw Hat Luffy!
He spent many years as a member of the Whitebeard Pirates.
He was already familiar with the territory,
so after their captain died,
Blackbeard wasted no time in seizing control of it for himself.
Using the Tremor Tremor fruit he stole upon Whitebeard's death.
He's gaining quite the reputation, along with Shanks, Kaido, and Big Mom.
He's joined the ranks of the Four Emperors.
So he stole Whitebeard's devil fruit and his title? Talk about a scumbag!
I agree, his audacity is infuriating.
There's a rumor going around that they're currently on the hunt for those with devil fruit powers.
I am not sure how it's possible, but it seems they found a way to acquire abilities from the other people upon killing them.
Clearly they plan to usurp the strongest powers they can find and become unstoppable.
Be on your guard!
No, they're gonna take mine!
The human-human fruit? I think you're safe.
You sure?
I worry for you the most, Luffy.
I know there's a great deal of bad blood between you and Teach.
You must take care.
Luffy!
Have you been listening to me?
Huh?
You're supposed to be the captain here!
The captain needs to have at least some idea of the situation!
Whoa. It's okay, Jinbei. The rest of us heard you.
Huh? I thought the captain was supposed to goof off while the crew looks out for him!
Shame on you, Luffy! A good captain dedicates his life to the safety of his crew, and here you are-
Don't be such a drag! I'd rather take my chances and see what happens! It's more fun that way!
I don't envy you all one bit!
Tell me about it!
Are you here, Luffy-chan?
There you are! The party's for you, you know! Why are all you guys hiding out?
Hey, Kami!
Oh, yeah. What happened to Weepy Hoshi? Did she leave?
She was tired. All the excitement made her need a little nap, so she went up to her room.
Hang on. Zoro? Sanji?
It seems like there's some kind of monster here.
You may be right. Yeah, I feel it too.
I never dreamed a party could be such fun. I might have to take a little nap just to recover from it all.
Have you ever been playing aroundre Chief-a?
Ah!
Are you…
It looks like there's no time to take care of the rest of the ship!
Well, it's possible that he wants to go to our new ship...
Eh.
Are you unaf fights against you?
Bah!
Ah!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, haa!
Ya!
Ah, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
The Mets
The End
Help me!
Shhh!
Oh, you please! I can't even help me!
Help me!
You cut me to the quick, princess!
Don't look so unhappy to see me!
Just relax.
I promise I won't do anything to cause you pain,
my dear.
I was ready to settle for just the treasure
after selling off the other mermaids turned out
to be a hassle, but you might just be
an exception!
Now then, I want you to be a good girl and go to sleep
for a little while. Can you do that for me?
I just received word from my brother.
He and the crew have made port on
Fishman Island. We're all headed
into the new world and we'd like
for you to come along with us!
Zuh!
Now now. Show me a smile!
He he he he he he
He he he he he he he he he!
You! Oh what do you want, Straw Hat?
Go find your own mermaid princess.
We're busy!
Rafi!
King!
It's you!
Wolfie!
Oh!
That guy was still here.
Wolfie!
That was scary! Thank you for saving me!
Luffy, you lucky bastard! I should have kicked him while I had the chance!
Wasn't that the pirate we captured not too long ago?
I haven't seen him since we left the island. Hell, I haven't even thought about him.
Oh well, I guess he's gone now.
That was a close call. We really can't thank you enough, Luffy.
It's no big deal.
That ruffian who stole from us! I can't believe he was still nearby!
This place is usually locked up so tight even a guppy can't get in.
But with everything that's happened, it seems we left it open.
And look! That big tower over there has been sliced clean in two!
The robber must have done it while we were out in the plaza!
Sorry, actually that would be this guy. Man, you should have seen him.
When they got out of the cage, he was hacking and slashing all over the block!
Please, learn to keep your mouth shut, stupid starfish!
I don't think so! If I don't say something, that makes me an accomplice!
Hey, righty, here's a question.
Righty?
You mentioned a treasure thief, right?
Yes, you heard correctly. That unsavory man who was just here snuck into the palace and robbed us blind.
Really? Well then...
Here we go again!
You're gonna let him steal national treasures?
Now that my people are safe from harm, I care nothing for material riches.
Oh, cut the crap!
Wait, so you're saying you don't want them anymore?
If you can rescue them, you're free to keep them. It's the least I can do for our heroes.
Well, if you insist!
Ugh!
You idiots just had to kick him into next week, didn't you? Why couldn't you just knock him out and tie him up in the tower?
Oh, Nami, you're so cute!
Go catch him and bring him back!
Get back!
Your Majesty!
Hmm?
It's Hordy and his men, sir! Their handcuffs came off!
But how?
Ho!
Damn you humans!
Don't think we've forgotten our grudge!
We'll exact our revenge soon enough!
Then Storhead'll be the first to die!
Bring him to my cell!
Oh, my back hurts! I sure could use a drink!
I aged myself on purpose!
I want to get back at the Straw Hats, but my energy's at an old time low soon!
We won't show them an ounce of mercy!
What in the world has happened here?
Don't tell me!
Is that Hordy and his crew?
You think these guys can hold me?
What a bunch of morons!
I'll break them and...
Captain Hordy!
Why are they so brittle?
Just as I thought!
That energy steroid you were taking to make yourself stronger!
And the pill from inside the Tamate Box!
They're one and the same, aren't they?
A Tamate Box?
A priceless artifact passed down for generations, Jamal!
The pills hidden inside were highly valuable as well!
But ten years ago someone stole them from us!
We failed to catch the culprit!
His Majesty was concerned that a scandal might break out, so we closed the case!
Actually, Hordy, I think that happened around the same time you left the army!
Interesting!
Of course it was me!
Look what's happened to my body!
Need me to spill it out for you!
The pills were treasured heirloans.
The truth behind their purpose lost long ago.
Tales of their power and the curse that accompanied them were both passed down merely as legend.
But still, enough to make us wary.
It would appear that our discretion was warranted, however.
The Tamate Box was carefully guarded for the safety of our people.
This result is truly regrettable.
If you had not allowed your judgment to be clouded by foolish dreams of power,
you would not have subjected yourselves to this terrible fate.
What the hell do you know?
In any case, they'll never get their vengeance now.
You'll see!
The heavens have chosen us to settle the score, and that's just what we'll do!
And we'll not only wipe out the human race,
we'll annihilate you and your entire family!
I pity them.
Perhaps I ought to offer them clemency.
Wait, Captain!
Fukumoshi, you're a disgrace to our people!
Fishman Island is healing now.
So although you killed my mother, I will not hold a grudge.
The least that you can do is refrain from speaking.
I don't want the children hearing your poisonous words.
Minister of the Left!
Huh?
Baron Tamago!
And Mr. Peikums!
They're at the Sweets Factory!
They're here to collect for Big Mom.
We can't face them now.
Hand over the Sweets!
Gah!
Don't keep Mama waiting.
Toot Sweet.
We don't have any sweets for this month's payment!
Hordy and his lackeys tore the factory apart!
And all the candy we could salvage was sent to the banquet so the Straw Hats could enjoy it!
What should we do?
Something tells me Big Mom of the Four Emperors won't be satisfied with an apology.
That woman would level an entire country for sweets!
While the Straw Hats rush to retrieve Fishman Island's stolen treasure, pirates working for Big Mom appear.
After scarcely avoiding destruction at Hordy's hand, the island is now under threat from an even stronger adversary.
Luffy steps up to save the Fishman once again, but may doom himself by antagonizing one of the strongest pirates in the New World.
On the next, One Piece!
She loves sweets!
Big Mom of the Four Emperors!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!